import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> hunterQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of Gon Freecss’s father?",
      answer1: "Ging Freecss",
      answer2: "Goku",
      answer3: "Whis",
      answer4: "Grad Priest",
      correctAnswer: "Whis"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many people didn’t pass the 287th Hunter Exam?",
      answer1: "One",
      answer2: "Two",
      answer3: "Three",
      answer4: "Four",
      correctAnswer: "Two"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the leader of Phantom Troupe?",
      answer1: "Chrollo Lucilfer",
      answer2: "Nobunaga Hazama",
      answer3: "Feitan Portor",
      answer4: "Franklin Bordeau",
      correctAnswer: "Chrollo Lucilfer"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Gon’s birthplace?",
      answer1: "Greed Island",
      answer2: "Whale Island",
      answer3: "Yorknew City",
      answer4: "Meteor Citt",
      correctAnswer: "Whale Island"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Phantom Troupe consists of how many members?",
      answer1: "Ten Members",
      answer2: "Eleven Members",
      answer3: "Twelve Members",
      answer4: "Thirteen Members",
      correctAnswer: "Thirteen Members"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Kurapika’s codename in Zodiac group?",
      answer1: "Dragon",
      answer2: "Tiger",
      answer3: "Rat",
      answer4: "Rabbit",
      correctAnswer: "Rat"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the starting point of Greed Island video game?",
      answer1: "Shiso Tree",
      answer2: "Masadora",
      answer3: "Soufrabi",
      answer4: "Aiai",
      correctAnswer: "Shiso Tree"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Killua's Sister name?",
      answer1: "Kite",
      answer2: "Shiziku Murasaki",
      answer3: "Alluka Zoldyck",
      answer4: "Cheadle Yorkshire",
      correctAnswer: "Alluka Zoldyck"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of Kurapika’s Nen teacher?",
      answer1: "Wing",
      answer2: "Izunavi",
      answer3: "Netero",
      answer4: "Beans",
      correctAnswer: "Izunavi"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many floors does Heavens Arena have?",
      answer1: "252 floors",
      answer2: "263 floors",
      answer3: "251 floors",
      answer4: "262 floors",
      correctAnswer: "251 floors"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which one of the following isn’t Killua’s brother?",
      answer1: "Illumi",
      answer2: "Milluki",
      answer3: "Alluka",
      answer4: "Kalluto",
      correctAnswer: "Alluka"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Tonpa’s examinee number in 287th Hunter Exam?",
      answer1: "Fifty One",
      answer2: "Fourty three",
      answer3: "Twent Eight",
      answer4: "Sixteen",
      correctAnswer: "Sixteen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the spider that Kurapika killed in Yorknew City Arc?",
      answer1: "Uvogin",
      answer2: "Shalnark",
      answer3: "Pakunoda",
      answer4: "Kortopi",
      correctAnswer: "Uvogin"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is Gon Freecss’s Japanese voice actor? (2011 anime)",
      answer1: "Megumi Han",
      answer2: "Junko Takeuchi",
      answer3: "Rikiya Koyama",
      answer4: "Mariya Ise",
      correctAnswer: "Megumi Han"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who said “Their eyes were stolen from every single body. All of them… Killed for what death creates. So I’ve sworn to capture the Phantom Troupe… And recover the eyes of my clan!!”",
      answer1: "Gon",
      answer2: "Killua",
      answer3: "Kurapika",
      answer4: "Hisoka",
      correctAnswer: "Kurapika"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of Killua's grandfather?",
      answer1: "Zeno",
      answer2: "Silva",
      answer3: "Kora",
      answer4: "Maha",
      correctAnswer: "Zeno"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who's the youngest in the Zoldyck brothers?",
      answer1: "Kalluto",
      answer2: "Milluki",
      answer3: "Killua",
      answer4: "Alluka",
      correctAnswer: "Kalluto"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who's the youngest in the Zoldyck brothers?",
      answer1: "Kalluto",
      answer2: "Milluki",
      answer3: "Killua",
      answer4: "Alluka",
      correctAnswer: "Kalluto"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "When is Hisoka's birthday?",
      answer1: "June 6",
      answer2: "July 17",
      answer3: "December 12",
      answer4: "April 5",
      correctAnswer: "June 6"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was the winner of \"Greed Island\" game?",
      answer1: "Gon",
      answer2: "Lillua",
      answer3: "Hisuka",
      answer4: "Bisuke",
      correctAnswer: "Gon"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which Phantom Troupe member has holes in his body?",
      answer1: "Bonolenov",
      answer2: "Shuzuku",
      answer3: "Feitan",
      answer4: "Uvo",
      correctAnswer: "Bonolenov"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the aunt of Gon?",
      answer1: "Luka",
      answer2: "Mito",
      answer3: "Mika",
      answer4: "Gina",
      correctAnswer: "Mito"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Kurapika's age at the beginning of Hunter x Hunter?",
      answer1: "Sixteen",
      answer2: "Seventeen",
      answer3: "Eighteen",
      answer4: "Nineteen",
      correctAnswer: "Seventeen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Kaito/Kite belongs with of these following nen users:",
      answer1: "Conjurers",
      answer2: "Enhancers",
      answer3: "Transmuters",
      answer4: "Specialists",
      correctAnswer: "Conjurers"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Kaito/Kite belongs with of these following nen users:",
      answer1: "Conjurers",
      answer2: "Enhancers",
      answer3: "Transmuters",
      answer4: "Specialists",
      correctAnswer: "Conjurers"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What color is Killua's hair?",
      answer1: "Grey",
      answer2: "Silver",
      answer3: "White",
      answer4: "Yellow",
      correctAnswer: "Silver"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who had a red hair in HXH?",
      answer1: "Gon",
      answer2: "Kurapika",
      answer3: "Hisuka",
      answer4: "Killua",
      correctAnswer: "Hisuka"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which clan does kurapika belong to?",
      answer1: "Kurta",
      answer2: "Zoldyc",
      answer3: "Mira",
      answer4: "None of them",
      correctAnswer: "Kurta"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "when is killua's birthday in the 2011 series?",
      answer1: "July 7",
      answer2: "May 25",
      answer3: "June 5",
      answer4: "July 6",
      correctAnswer: "July 7"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "When was Killua's first appearance?",
      answer1: "Episode 5",
      answer2: "Episode 6",
      answer3: "Episode 7",
      answer4: "Episode 8",
      correctAnswer: "Episode 6"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who had a blonde hair",
      answer1: "Kurapika",
      answer2: "Gon",
      answer3: "Killua",
      answer4: "Hisoka",
      correctAnswer: "Kurapika"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What colour is Ging's eye (2011)?",
      answer1: "Green",
      answer2: "Blue",
      answer3: "Brown",
      answer4: "None of them",
      correctAnswer: "Brown"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "At episode 93 (2011) , Gon was dating with ?",
      answer1: "Palm",
      answer2: "Shiziku",
      answer3: "Neon",
      answer4: "None of them",
      correctAnswer: "Palm"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is Neferpitou's voice actor?",
      answer1: "Erika Harlacher",
      answer2: "Ayumi Fujimura",
      answer3: "Megumi Han",
      answer4: "Issei Futamata",
      correctAnswer: "Ayumi Fujimura"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Hunter X Hunter Data Book 2004 listed Milluki as a ?",
      answer1: "Manipulator",
      answer2: "Enhancer",
      answer3: "Specialist",
      answer4: "Conjurer",
      correctAnswer: "Manipulator"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "which sword did hisoka break in his fight with kurapica in hunter exam?",
      answer1: "Left",
      answer2: "Right",
      answer3: "Didn't break any sword",
      answer4: "Didn't use a sword",
      correctAnswer: "Right"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "how old was kurapika when the kurta clan was massacred?",
      answer1: "Twelve",
      answer2: "Thirteen",
      answer3: "Fourteen",
      answer4: "Fifteen",
      correctAnswer: "Twelve"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "According to the final episode from OVA 3 \"G.I Final\",what was the name of card no.000?",
      answer1: "A warm reception from ruler",
      answer2: "A rulers banquet",
      answer3: "A ruler's blessing",
      answer4: "A ruler's invitaion",
      correctAnswer: "A ruler's blessing"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Where did Gon's Mother die?",
      answer1: "In her house",
      answer2: "In a ship in the sea",
      answer3: "In a horse in the desert",
      answer4: "In a boat in the sea",
      correctAnswer: "In a ship in the sea"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Hisoka is member of phantom troup, what number he is?",
      answer1: "Six",
      answer2: "Eight",
      answer3: "Four",
      answer4: "Twelve",
      correctAnswer: "Four"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Hisoka is member of phantom troup, what number he is?",
      answer1: "Six",
      answer2: "Eight",
      answer3: "Four",
      answer4: "Twelve",
      correctAnswer: "Four"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "who is Gon's Father?",
      answer1: "Ging",
      answer2: "Chrollo",
      answer3: "Kite",
      answer4: "Meruem",
      correctAnswer: "Ging"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was the first member of the troup to die",
      answer1: "Uvo",
      answer2: "Hisoka",
      answer3: "Shiziku",
      answer4: "Machi",
      correctAnswer: "Uvo"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "how tall is gon?",
      answer1: "154 cm",
      answer2: "145 cm",
      answer3: "150 cm",
      answer4: "158 cm",
      correctAnswer: "154 cm"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Feitan's blood type?",
      answer1: "A",
      answer2: "O",
      answer3: "B",
      answer4: "None of them",
      correctAnswer: "O"
  ),

];

// 45 questions